<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AI Square&#39;s HyperSpeak - Revolutionize Your Meetings on AI Square</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AI Square&#39;s HyperSpeak - Revolutionize Your Meetings on AI Square</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Savva | CSO</title>
      <link>/team/nicolassavva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/nicolassavva/</guid>
      <description>Meet Nicolas Savva: A Visionary in Computer Graphics and AI Nicolas Savva, our Chief Science Officer and co-founder, brings unparalleled expertise from his tenure at Cornell University, where he earned his M.S./Ph.D., and briefly served as a lecturer. His exceptional capabilities have been recognized with the prestigious O-1 U.S. visa for individuals with extraordinary abilities.
Academic Excellence and Professional Accomplishments Nicolas&amp;rsquo;s academic journey at Cornell University laid a strong foundation for his career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Geddes</title>
      <link>/team/jamesgeddes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/jamesgeddes/</guid>
      <description>Meet James Geddes: Pioneering Engineer Driving Innovation at AI Square James Geddes is the Head of Engineering at AI Square, where he leverages his extensive expertise in software development, blockchain technology, and AI to propel the company&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking solutions forward. With a career marked by innovation and excellence, James is a driving force behind AI Square&amp;rsquo;s mission to revolutionize the future of work, education, and communication.
A Journey Through Technological Innovation James&amp;rsquo;s journey began at the University of Minnesota, where he played a pivotal role in advanced research on neutrino detection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Duval | CTO</title>
      <link>/team/nicolasduval/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/nicolasduval/</guid>
      <description>Meet Nicolas Duval: A Pioneer in Software Architecture and Innovation With a robust career spanning over 16 years, Nicolas Duval stands out as a beacon in the realms of software architecture, design, development, and management. His profound expertise in cloud computing, rapid prototyping, computer-aided design, machine learning, generative AI, and application development has paved the way for innovative breakthroughs in the field of software engineering.
A Journey of Innovation Nicolas&amp;rsquo;s journey in the tech industry is marked by significant contributions and leadership roles at some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most renowned technology companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accenture</title>
      <link>/partners/accenture/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/accenture/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Complete</title>
      <link>/partners/codecomplete/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/codecomplete/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte</title>
      <link>/partners/deloitte/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/deloitte/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hutchinson</title>
      <link>/partners/huchinston/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/huchinston/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JMC</title>
      <link>/partners/jmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/jmc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nissan</title>
      <link>/partners/nissan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/nissan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Inception Member</title>
      <link>/partners/nvidia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/nvidia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shibuya Startup Support</title>
      <link>/partners/shibuya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/shibuya/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louis Boka | CEO</title>
      <link>/team/louisboka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/louisboka/</guid>
      <description>Meet Louis Boka: A Visionary in AI and Technology Louis Boka is a global citizen with a unique third-culture upbringing, driven by an insatiable quest to connect and understand diverse perspectives. From a young age, Louis was captivated by the immersive worlds of video games, which sparked his passion for design and technology. This fascination led him to delve into the world of computer graphics during his university years.
The Professional Journey Stepping into the professional realm, Louis quickly realized the transformative power of technology in solving complex business challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changi Airport Group</title>
      <link>/partners/cag/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/cag/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3Si</title>
      <link>/partners/3si/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/3si/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epiq Global</title>
      <link>/partners/epiq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/epiq/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI SQUARE</title>
      <link>/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 13:13:55 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Louis and I first crossed paths in 2011 while working at a startup in Montreal. Boasting backgrounds in computer graphics, our connection was almost immediate. Conversations ranged from the nitty-gritty of tech to broader, existential topics that questioned the very fabric of our reality.
In 2013, life pulled us in different directions. I relocated to San Francisco while Louis made Singapore his new home. On touching down in SF, I was met with an avalanche of new tech jargon: cloud computing, node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Computer Graphics engineer</title>
      <link>/careers/ml_software_engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/ml_software_engineer/</guid>
      <description>Company Overview At AI SQUARE, we&amp;rsquo;re at the intersection of machine learning&amp;rsquo;s vast potential and the limitless world of computer graphics. Pioneering and redefining boundaries, our goal is to produce immersive experiences that synthesize imagination with state-of-the-art technology.
Position Machine Learning &amp;amp; Computer Graphics Engineer
Location San Francisco or remote
Role Overview As our Machine Learning &amp;amp; Computer Graphics Engineer, you&amp;rsquo;ll play a crucial role in blending advanced algorithms with dynamic visual content, translating ideas into real-world applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platform Engineer (SaaS) </title>
      <link>/careers/platform-engineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/platform-engineer/</guid>
      <description>Company Overview At AI SQUARE, we&amp;rsquo;re at the intersection of machine learning&amp;rsquo;s vast potential and the limitless world of computer graphics. Pioneering and redefining boundaries, our goal is to produce immersive experiences that synthesize imagination with state-of-the-art technology.
Position Platform Engineer (SaaS)
Location San Francisco or remote
Role Overview As our Platform Engineer, you will be pivotal in building, optimizing, and maintaining the robust SaaS platforms that power our innovative solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Intern</title>
      <link>/careers/ml_intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/careers/ml_intern/</guid>
      <description>Company Overview At AI SQUARE, we&amp;rsquo;re at the intersection of machine learning&amp;rsquo;s vast potential and the limitless world of computer graphics. Pioneering and redefining boundaries, our goal is to produce immersive experiences that synthesize imagination with state-of-the-art technology.
Position Machine Learning Intern
Location San Francisco or remote
Role Overview As our Machine Learning Intern, you will be an essential part of a pioneering team, exploring the confluence of machine learning algorithms and dynamic visual content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow us on social media </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Page Example 1</title>
      <link>/custom-page-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom-page-1/</guid>
      <description>Markdown Content The markdown content can be placed between sections, not just at the end of the page. The markdown is still written like normal, it&amp;rsquo;s not inside a front-matter field (which would be overly restrictive)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investor Relations</title>
      <link>/investors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/investors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Approach</title>
      <link>/our-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-approach/</guid>
      <description>A Vision for the Future We believe that the true potential of AI isn&amp;rsquo;t just about amazing technology but in its ability to solve real-world, often overlooked challenges.
Harness AI&amp;rsquo;s capabilities to drive transformative change in underserved sectors, creating lasting value and impact. Co-creating the Future AI Square&amp;rsquo;s approach is rooted in collaboration.
Instead of developing solutions in isolation and pray for adoption, we work closely with industry partners, understanding their unique challenges and co-creating scalable AI solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inter-Link AI The Game-Changing AI Feature of HyperSpeak</title>
      <link>/information-integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/information-integrity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foxconn</title>
      <link>/partners/foxconn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 05:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partners/foxconn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Page 2</title>
      <link>/custom-page-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 04:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom-page-2/</guid>
      <description>Content Section Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, male! Quo sed hic die solido, gloria?
Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Page 3</title>
      <link>/custom-page-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 04:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom-page-3/</guid>
      <description>Content Section Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, male! Quo sed hic die solido, gloria?
Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning as a Service (MLaaS)</title>
      <link>/machine-learning-as-a-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 04:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/machine-learning-as-a-service/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Future, Delivered Today Untapped data is untapped potential. Harness it with AI Square&amp;rsquo;s Machine Learning as a Service (MLaaS).
We train AI models tailored for your needs with your data, and empower your business to lead with unparalleled competitive insight.
Turn your data into decisive actions, effortlessly. Dive into the future of decision-making, where your data drives every strategic move. Your AI advantage starts here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Heading Your privacy is important to us. It is Hugo Advance&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://hugo-advance-pro.netlify.com/, and other sites we own and operate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
