<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest research on AI Square</title>
    <link>/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Latest research on AI Square</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare</title>
      <link>/research/healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/healthcare/</guid>
      <description>AI-Enhanced 3D-Printed Prosthetics for Cranial Asymmetry In the world of healthcare, technological advancements are breaking new ground, and at the forefront of these innovations is the revolutionary field of AI-enhanced cranial care for infants with cranial asymmetry.
Cranial asymmetry, a condition characterized by the misshaping of an infant&amp;rsquo;s skull, has historically been addressed with corrective helmets. However, the traditional approach to designing these helmets has been time-consuming and costly.
Here, we dive into the groundbreaking techniques we&amp;rsquo;ve employed, integrating cutting-edge AI and 3D printing to create a faster, more cost-effective solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/research/infrastructure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/infrastructure/</guid>
      <description>Identifying the Challenges The realm of infrastructure, especially with its intrinsic integration with IoT devices, presents unique challenges.
Traditional hardware maintenance predominantly functions on reactive measures. This method, although common, is increasingly seen as inefficient due to the unplanned downtimes it often results in, leading to elevated operational costs and underutilized opportunities.
Investigating AI&amp;rsquo;s Potential in Infrastructure Our research is centered around exploring how Artificial Intelligence can be applied to transform this landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistics</title>
      <link>/research/logistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/logistics/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the Data Conundrum in Shipping The global shipping landscape is emblematic of a vast ecosystem teeming with intricate data streams. This includes an amalgamation of supply chain partners, digital dossiers, paper-based records, and client inputs.
Integral to the industry&amp;rsquo;s core, these data structures dictate everything from cargo allocation to destination routing.
However, the key challenge is evident: the onus of ensuring that information remains accurate, verifiable, and actionable. The consequence of a mere data discrepancy could spiral into significant logistical errors, affecting trade routes and incurring substantial economic implications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
