<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HyperSpeak Team on AI Square</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HyperSpeak Team on AI Square</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Savva | CSO</title>
      <link>/team/nicolassavva/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/nicolassavva/</guid>
      <description>Meet Nicolas Savva: A Visionary in Computer Graphics and AI Nicolas Savva, our Chief Science Officer and co-founder, brings unparalleled expertise from his tenure at Cornell University, where he earned his M.S./Ph.D., and briefly served as a lecturer. His exceptional capabilities have been recognized with the prestigious O-1 U.S. visa for individuals with extraordinary abilities.
Academic Excellence and Professional Accomplishments Nicolas&amp;rsquo;s academic journey at Cornell University laid a strong foundation for his career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Geddes</title>
      <link>/team/jamesgeddes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/jamesgeddes/</guid>
      <description>Meet James Geddes: Pioneering Engineer Driving Innovation at AI Square James Geddes is the Head of Engineering at AI Square, where he leverages his extensive expertise in software development, blockchain technology, and AI to propel the company&amp;rsquo;s groundbreaking solutions forward. With a career marked by innovation and excellence, James is a driving force behind AI Square&amp;rsquo;s mission to revolutionize the future of work, education, and communication.
A Journey Through Technological Innovation James&amp;rsquo;s journey began at the University of Minnesota, where he played a pivotal role in advanced research on neutrino detection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Duval | CTO</title>
      <link>/team/nicolasduval/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/nicolasduval/</guid>
      <description>Meet Nicolas Duval: A Pioneer in Software Architecture and Innovation With a robust career spanning over 16 years, Nicolas Duval stands out as a beacon in the realms of software architecture, design, development, and management. His profound expertise in cloud computing, rapid prototyping, computer-aided design, machine learning, generative AI, and application development has paved the way for innovative breakthroughs in the field of software engineering.
A Journey of Innovation Nicolas&amp;rsquo;s journey in the tech industry is marked by significant contributions and leadership roles at some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most renowned technology companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louis Boka | CEO</title>
      <link>/team/louisboka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/louisboka/</guid>
      <description>Meet Louis Boka: A Visionary in AI and Technology Louis Boka is a global citizen with a unique third-culture upbringing, driven by an insatiable quest to connect and understand diverse perspectives. From a young age, Louis was captivated by the immersive worlds of video games, which sparked his passion for design and technology. This fascination led him to delve into the world of computer graphics during his university years.
The Professional Journey Stepping into the professional realm, Louis quickly realized the transformative power of technology in solving complex business challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
