<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on AI Square</title>
    <link>/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on AI Square</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-us/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;At AI Square, our philosophy is simple: Pioneering AI research for genuine, lasting impact&amp;rdquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow us on social media </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Page Example 1</title>
      <link>/custom-page-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom-page-1/</guid>
      <description>Markdown Content The markdown content can be placed between sections, not just at the end of the page. The markdown is still written like normal, it&amp;rsquo;s not inside a front-matter field (which would be overly restrictive)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investor Relations</title>
      <link>/investors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/investors/</guid>
      <description>Join us in our mission to revolutionize industries with cutting-edge AI! &amp;ldquo;Can you solve this problem with AI?&amp;rdquo; After hearing this from clients for years we decided it was time to start AI Square.
We transform AI research into practical, sector-specific applications that yield measurable outcomes for our clients.
Market size The AI market valued at $100 billion has witnessed unparalleled growth in recent years, proving to be an indispensable catalyst for global innovation and business transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Approach</title>
      <link>/our-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-approach/</guid>
      <description>A Vision for the Future We believe that the true potential of AI isn&amp;rsquo;t just about amazing technology but in its ability to solve real-world, often overlooked challenges.
Harness AI&amp;rsquo;s capabilities to drive transformative change in underserved sectors, creating lasting value and impact. Co-creating the Future AI Square&amp;rsquo;s approach is rooted in collaboration.
Instead of developing solutions in isolation and pray for adoption, we work closely with industry partners, understanding their unique challenges and co-creating scalable AI solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Information Integrity Platform</title>
      <link>/information-integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:14:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/information-integrity/</guid>
      <description>Imagine a World&amp;hellip; Where data, no matter its origin or format, is unified, correlated, and verified.
Revolutionary Simplicity We didn&amp;rsquo;t just solve a tech puzzle; we pioneered a paradigm shift.
Our platform isn&amp;rsquo;t just a tool, it&amp;rsquo;s a promise. A commitment to ensuring that your data, whether handwritten, digital, or spoken, stands unified &amp;amp; unbreakable. Results Beyond Numbers Our impact Transcends the Digital, it changes the course of businesses.
Reclaim thousands of hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Page 2</title>
      <link>/custom-page-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 04:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom-page-2/</guid>
      <description>Content Section Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, male! Quo sed hic die solido, gloria?
Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Page 3</title>
      <link>/custom-page-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 04:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/custom-page-3/</guid>
      <description>Content Section Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, male! Quo sed hic die solido, gloria?
Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus. Memorata haberet sepulcrales gentisque dum sic, in flumina templa! Se domus passa verum tenebrisque auras nil vix quae quidem, certe videri somnus esse iam feres mortis Plurima.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning as a Service (MLaaS)</title>
      <link>/machine-learning-as-a-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 04:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/machine-learning-as-a-service/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Future, Delivered Today Untapped data is untapped potential. Harness it with AI Square&amp;rsquo;s Machine Learning as a Service (MLaaS).
We train AI models tailored for your needs with your data, and empower your business to lead with unparalleled competitive insight.
Turn your data into decisive actions, effortlessly. Dive into the future of decision-making, where your data drives every strategic move. Your AI advantage starts here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
